<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hamburg</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="about">About Application</string>
    <string name="help">Need help</string>
    <string name="about_content">
        This is an application designed inside the program of Google Developer Challenge Scholarship
        track Android Basic. This is a demo of using Fragment to create an application with multiscreens
    </string>
    <string name="help_content">
        All code is hosted in this github repository. Feel free to contact me for further information
    </string>
    <string name="account">User account</string>
    <string name="saved">Saved items</string>
    <string name="account_content">Will be updated later</string>
    <string name="saved_content">Will be updated later</string>
    <string name="seen">seen</string>
    <string name="general">What do you know about Hamburg?</string>
    <string name="sightseeing">What to see?</string>
    <string name="activity">What to do?</string>
    <string name="food">What to eat?</string>
    <string name="transport">How to move?</string>
    <string name="accomodation">Where to sleep?</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="location_text">
        Hamburg,also as known as Free and Hanseatic Hamburg. It is the second largest city in Germany,
        locates in the nord of the country
    </string>
    <string name="population">Population</string>
    <string name="population_text">It has a population of 1.8 milliion people</string>
    <string name="weather_content">
        The weather in Hamburg is especially nice in summer, which is from
        Juni to August. In winter it\'s quite cold and rains a lot
    </string>
    <string name="weather">Weather</string>
    <string name="ranking">Ranking</string>
    <string name="ranking_content">
        The city is a tourist destination for both domestic and international
        visitors, ranked 18th in the world for livability in 2016
    </string>
    <string name="harbour">Hamburg Harbour</string>
    <string name="harbour_text">
        Hamburg Habour is one of the most important harbours in Germany.
        With a long walk and coast, you can either go on foot along this or take a
        ferry. Hamburg harbour is also one of most popular places, where people
        go to in summer for sunbathing. Harbour\'s birthday is in May and there are
        thousands of tourists every year there"
    </string>
    <string name="reeperbahn">Hamburg Reeperbahn</string>
    <string name="reeperbahn_text">
        Located in the center of the city, Reeperbahn is one of the most famous places in Hamburg.
        It\'s as known as the Redlight district. The whole area is very active at night.
        There are bunch of restaurants, bars, discos, sex shops, dancing clubs etc.
        If you visit Hamburg, it\'s one of the place you can not miss
    </string>
    <string name="city_hall">City Hall</string>
    <string name="city_hall_text">
        Also as known as the work place of parliament.This is actually the new city whole,
        which was built after the historical flame in Hamburg.
        An amazing architect design with a large square in front of.
        If you are walking down the city, don\'t forget to drop over here
    </string>
    <string name="lake">Alster Lake</string>
    <string name="lake_text">
        A long and large lake in the heart of the city,
        Alster lake is one of the most relaxing places.
        There are a lot of coffee shops around the lake.
        If you go to Hamburg in summer, don\'t forget to hire
        a bike and drive around the lake. In middle of the
        lake there is the a huge sculpture of a lady bathing.
    </string>
    <string name="hafencity">Hafencity</string>
    <string name="hafencity_text">
        This is the new part of Hamburg with modern architect. Take
        some time and walk around. It has an amazing design
        and is very warm in winter and cool in summer.This
        is where the whole entertainment companies locate,
        as well as offices and international firms
    </string>
    <string name="church">Churches</string>
    <string name="church_text">
        As known as one of the biggest cities for evanglish.
        Hamburg has in total 5 biggest churches, which you can
        even see from above(for example from Dockland in habour).
        There are some very old churches from 2. World War,
        which they want to keep as a historical sign, to remind
        everyone of the dark side of the war
    </string>
    <string name="museum">Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_text">
        They city gives you a huge variety of museum,
        from art to technology.Take a look at the city map and decide to visit
        some. I would recommend the maritime museum with 9 stocks of all small,
        big models of ships, the electricity museum with all old devices
        from the beginning of electricity. A tour to underground of Hamburg
        is also one thing you should not miss. Remember to book it as soon as
        possible, because it normally takes over a week to  get it
    </string>
    <string name="fish_market">Fish market</string>
    <string name="fish_market_text">
        Every sunday morning from 8 to 10:30.
        If you love to enjoy the fresh air of the hanseatic city,
        don\'t miss the fish market. Go to buy some fish, fresh
        vegetables or fruit and take a fresh breathe in the morning in the harbour.
        Your day will be a good day</string>
    <string name="water_light"><![CDATA[Water light in <Planten und Blomen>]]></string>
    <string name="water_light_text">
        An amazing water play with classical music. Only available in summer
    </string>
    <string name="dungeon">Hamburg Dungeon</string>
    <string name="dungeon_text">
        A 90-minute tour through the history of Hamburg with a very real feeling from
        a profession theater team. From the historical flame, which destroyed
        two third of the city till the epidemics, which killed almost people
    </string>
    <string name="miniatur">Miniatur</string>
    <string name="miniatur_text">
        There is a collection of small models of a lot of famous city
        in the world. A small and detail, as real as unbelievable
    </string>
    <string name="dialog">Dialog im Dunkel</string>
    <string name="dialog_text">Have you ever wonder what\'s
        like to like as a blind. Here is a place where you can try it.
        Try to live, eat and work all in the darkness
    </string>
    <string name="planet">Planetarium</string>
    <string name="planet_text">
        If you are a fan a universe, don\'t forget to come over here. They have amazing shows every
        week for very reasonable price. Take a seat and let you fly to the moon, the galaxy far far away...
    </string>
    <string name="shopping">Shopping centers</string>
    <string name="shopping_text">
        If you are a fan of shopping, you are in the right place. There are shopping streets, shopping malls,
        shopping centers every where in the city
    </string>
    <string name="musical">Musical theaters</string>
    <string name="musical_text">
        It\'s a must if you visit Hamburg. Five famous musical theaters
        with amazing effect and actors gives you a real feeling like playing
        a role in the play. They are quite expensive, around
        100 euro per person. But if you have the chance, don\'t miss it
    </string>
    <string name="sternschanzen">Sternschanzen</string>
    <string name="sternschanzen_text">
        A coffee or a  dinner? You are in the eating street of Hamburg
    </string>
    <string name="fleamarket">Fleamarket</string>
    <string name="fleamarket_text">
        There are a lot of flea markets in Hamburg on weekend. The biggest one locates near train station Feldstraße
        There are second hand products but very good quality for a cheap price.
    </string>
    <string name="dom">Hamburger Dom</string>
    <string name="dom_text">
        Twice a year. Hamburger Dom is a entertainment place with tons of game and food
    </string>
    <string name="christmas">Christmas markets</string>
    <string name="christmas_text">
        If you are here on christmas, you are very lucky. Go along some christmas market here
        to feel the warmth of fried potato or try some Glühwein
    </string>
    <string name="ice">Eis skating in park</string>
    <string name="ice_text">
        A eis skating place locates in the border of Planten und Blomen
    </string>
    <string name="picnic">Picnic in parks</string>
    <string name="picnic_text">
        Give you some relaxing time and lay down lazy in the park.
        Taking a nap or meeting with friends is both good choices
        to relax in summer
    </string>
    <string name="food1">A German has to know at least 21 dishes from potato</string>
    <string name="food1_t">
        Try as many dishes from potato as possibe, they are all german traditional food</string>
    <string name="food2">German Beer</string>
    <string name="food2_t">
        It\'s a must. There are very good beer in Germany in general. Come over some bars and order different types of beer.</string>
    <string name="food3">Asia food</string>
    <string name="food3_t">
        In every corner of Hamburg. The city is a mixture of local people and immigrant. There are ton of vietnamese,
        thailand, indonesian, chinese restaurants all around the city
    </string>
    <string name="food4">Breakfast(Brunch)</string>
    <string name="food4_t">
        A huge breakfast buffet with german tradition bread, cheese and fishes. Let\'s be german for a day</string>
    <string name="food5">German Fast food</string>
    <string name="food5_t">
        The hanseatic city offers you fish bread and seafood in every corner. American fastfood is also easy
        to find</string>
    <string name="other">Others</string>
    <string name="other_t">
        Italian, Greece or whatever you want, you will find it here</string>
    <string name="train">Train</string>
    <string name="train_t">
        The city has an amazing public transportation. There are around 10 underground trains going around the city
        every day.
    </string>
    <string name="bus">Bus</string>
    <string name="bus_t">
        For the same ticket as train, you can take any bus and see the city from the window
    </string>
    <string name="bike">Bicycle</string>
    <string name="bike_t">
        Stadtrad is a project of the city to support protecting environment.
        Be sure to sign in for Stadtrad before you come,
        since it costs only 5 euro for signing and
        you get 30 minutes free for each tour
    </string>
    <string name="foot">On foot</string>
    <string name="foot_t">Walking around the city is not a bad idea as well</string>
    <string name="hotel">Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_t">
        If you are quite flexible with finance, find you a comfortable hotel
    </string>
    <string name="hostel">Hostel</string>
    <string name="hostel_t">
        If you are a student, then hostel is not a bad idea at all.
        20-30euro for a night with warm bath and breakfast included
    </string>
    <string name="air">Airbnb</string>
    <string name="air_t" >
        It\'s also very popular in a tourist attraction city like Hamburg</string>
    <string name="couch_surfing">Couchsurfing</string>
    <string name="couch_surfing_t">
        If you prefer to know some local people, go to couchsurfing
        and ask for a accomodation. People in Hamburg are very friendly and hospital
    </string>
    <string name="t1">general</string>
    <string name="t2">sightseeing</string>
    <string name="t3">activities</string>
    <string name="t4">food</string>
    <string name="t5">transportation</string>
    <string name="t6">accomodation</string>
    <string name="setting">System setting</string>
    <string name="setting_t">Will be updated later</string>

</resources>
